<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="https://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>

	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[UAE]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[UAE]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[42e7affe-0f39-4cd5-bb8d-2b673fb6c993]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE to India travel: Rule related to passport eased for Overseas Citizen of India card holders]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[UAE to India travel: Rule related to passport eased for Overseas Citizen of India card holders]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Indian Embassy in Abu Dhabi issues advisory for OCI cardholders travelling to India]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/uae-to-india-travel-rule-related-to-passport-eased-for-overseas-citizen-of-india-card-holders-1.78263753</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Sajila Saseendran, Senior Reporter]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[UAE to India travel: Rule eased for some passengers]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Abu Dhabi: The Indian government has eased some travel rules for Overseas Citizen of India (OCI) cardholders, according to an advisory issued by the Indian Embassy in Abu Dhabi on Thursday.</p>
<p>The mission took to Twitter to post the advisory for OCI cardholders and said the Indian government has exempted them from carrying their old passports that are linked to their valid OCI cards while travelling to India.</p>
<p>“The government of India (GoI), with a view to avoid inconvenience to OCI cardholders, has decided to allow OCI cardholders to enter India on the strength of their existing OCI cards, bearing old passport number, along with the new passport, without the need to carry their old passport,” the advisory stated.</p>
<p>However, carrying the new passport is a mandatory requirement, the mission reminded in the advisory.</p>
<p>OCI card is a long-term visa for Indian-origin people with citizenship of other countries. In the UAE, the Indian mission gets requests for OCI card-related services from people of Indian-origin who have obtained citizenship of other countries either by birth or by surrendering their Indian passport.</p>
<h3>Indian-American stranded in Dubai</h3>
<p>Some OCI cardholders had faced travel issues for not carrying their old passport linked to their OCI card.</p>
<p>On March 4, <em>Gulf News</em> had reported one such case in which an Indian-origin man from the United States was stranded in Dubai airport while he was on his way to attend his father’s funeral in India.</p>
<p>Based on his plea seeking help on Twitter, the Indian Consulate in Dubai had come to his rescue and helped him continue his journey by instantly issuing him an entry visa to India.</p>
<p>It is understood that such incidents were taken into consideration by the Indian government, following which the rule related to passport was relaxed.</p>
<p>Now that the government has clarified that the old passport linked to the OCI card is not mandatory for entering India, OCI cardholders will not have to face such difficulties during their journey to India.</p><a href="https://twitter.com/indembabudhabi/status/1377547367763873793?s=21" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>
<div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read more</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/us-based-indian-stuck-in-dubai-airport-on-way-to-attend-fathers-funeral-in-india-gets-help-1.77575836">US-based Indian stuck in Dubai airport on way to attend father’s funeral in India gets help
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/opinion/op-eds/kerala-elections-2021-candidate-watch-thomas-issac-g-sudhakaran-and-v-muraleedharan---ministers-top-leaders-among-notable-omissions-1.1617196324189">Kerala Elections 2021 Candidate Watch: Thomas Issac, G Sudhakaran and V Muraleedharan - ministers, top leaders among notable omissions 
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/indias-daily-new-covid-19-infections-highest-in-more-than-five-months-1.78259413">India’s daily new COVID-19 infections highest in more than five months
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/us-envoy-kerry-heads-to-india-to-try-and-lift-climate-ambition-1.78261685">US envoy Kerry heads to India to try and lift ‘climate ambition’
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/west-bengal-elections-2021-mamata-suvendu-face-off-in-battleground-nandigram-today-1.78249775">West Bengal elections 2021: Mamata-Suvendu face off in battleground Nandigram today
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<h3>Deadline extension</h3>
<p>In addition to this relaxation, the GoI has also extended the timeline for the requirement of re-issuance of OCI cards, the advisory said. Those OCI cardholders, who may be required to get their OCI cards re-issued, have now been given time until December 31, 2021.</p>
<p>“OCI cardholders are requested to kindly note the above guidelines before proceeding on any travel to India,” the mission added in the advisory.</p>
<p>The Indian Consulate in Dubai, which also issued a similar advisory for OCI cardholders, clarified that OCI cardholders are required to get their cards re-issued in two scenarios — each time a new passport is issued up to the age of 20 years and once after completing 50 years of age.</p><a href="https://twitter.com/cgidubai/status/1377592898661707779" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>
]]></description>
		<guid>1.78263753</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78263753]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 16:00:16+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 17:35:36+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2011/1/17/1_16a07f7fdd6.747804_1115256791_16a07f7fdd6_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2011/1/17/1_16a07f7fdd6.747804_1115256791_16a07f7fdd6_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[The newly-opened Indian Embassy building in Abu Dhabi.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[UAE]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[UAE]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[42e7affe-0f39-4cd5-bb8d-2b673fb6c993]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[From ‘unannounced’ KHDA visits to a 'wedding in the skies' — April Fool’s Day pranks stump netizens]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[From ‘unannounced’ KHDA visits to a 'wedding in the skies' — April Fool’s Day pranks stump netizens]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Twitterati who responded were in splits after realising they had fallen for the pranks]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/from-unannounced-khda-visits-to-a-wedding-in-the-skies--april-fools-day-pranks-stump-netizens-1.78259469</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Sajila Saseendran, Senior Reporter]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[KHDA moots unannounced home inspection. Are you ready?]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Dubai: An early-morning tweet by Dubai’s Knowledge and Human Development Authority (KHDA) about the start of unannounced home inspections for students made at least some netizens wonder if the authority would be invading their privacy.</p>
<p>“Due to ongoing distance learning, school inspectors will now begin unannounced visits to family homes. Ratings of each family will be published online to ensure students are receiving adequate support, sleep and chocolate,” the tweet said.</p><a href="https://twitter.com/Xyphynn/status/1377490178768527362" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>

<p>Seemingly concerned, Twitter user Keegan Dsouza posted: “Isnt that an invasion of privacy or something? (sic)”</p>
<p>However, most of the Twitterati, who responded, seemed to be in splits after realising that it was only an April Fool’s Day prank.</p>
<p>“Great. Thanks for the heads up, we’ll transform the house to achieve outstanding!!,” Audrey tweeted with ROFL emojis.</p>
<h3>Wedding Service at 40,000 feet</h3>
<p>Netizens were also seen falling for an announcement by Emirates airline to host special wedding service on its Airbus A380 on select routes.</p><a href="https://twitter.com/logankugler/status/1377295110413635591" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>

<p>“We’re taking love to new heights! Emirates is pleased to launch a special Wedding Service for those who want to tie the knot at 40,000 feet. Plan your perfect day on our @Airbus A380, now available on select routes,” the tweet posted on Wednesday evening said. A dream wedding picture of a couple holding hands on board a decked-up luxury cabin accompanied the tweet.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Emirates_1788c6de1dd_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Screenshot for the tweet from Emirates.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Supplied</span></figcaption>
<p>The ‘Just Married’ board amid the decorations showed the date 01.04.21, giving a hint to the social media followers about the prank.</p>
<p>“I want to get married like this in the future. Arrange it for me @keerthiravi2198 @performsegue, please,” posted Praveen Thirumurugan.</p>
<p>Logan Kugler, whose Twitter profile indicated that he is a writer on tech affairs, went a step ahead and asked for more details.</p>
<p>“Is there a link for more information and pricing about this somewhere? I might want to publish an article about this,” his post read.</p>
<p>Having been familar with Emirates’ history of coming up with different pranks on April Fool’s Day in the previous years, many other followers, however, conveyed how they enjoyed this one too.</p>
<p>“April fools? We can see that 1/4/2021 We are still waiting for ur chauffeur-less drones, triple decker n see thro-lounge. But still the best airlines without all of these (sic),” posted Joe.</p>
<p>Social media accounts of both KHDA and Emirates have been known for sharing tongue-in-cheek posts on numerous occasions. The April Fool’s editions are just the icing on the cake amid the stress and tensions of a COVID-19 pandemic.</p><div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read more</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/education/uae-has-over-295000-higher-education-students-says-new-report-1.78194835">UAE has over 295,000 higher education students, says new report
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/education/ramadan-in-a-pandemic-we-will-still-count-our-blessings-and-celebrate-1.1617107149411">Ramadan in a pandemic: We will still count our blessings and celebrate!
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/education/uks-international-stream-olympiads-appoints-trusity-as-headquarters-in-uae-1.1617104418638">UK’s International STREAM Olympiads appoints Trusity as headquarters in UAE
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/education/after-other-uk-boards-cambridge-igcse-a-levels-now-also-cancelled-in-uae-1.78192834">After other UK boards, Cambridge IGCSE, A-Levels now also ‘cancelled’ in UAE
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<p>April Fool’s Day is an annual custom of throwing practical pranks and spreading harmless hoaxes on April 1. Mass media can be involved in these pranks, which may be revealed later in the day or the following day.</p>
<p>One origin of the day is attributed to France shifting from the Julian calendar to the Gregorian calendar in 1582. After the switch, citizens who failed to recognise the change of New Year to January 1 and kept celebrating April 1 as New Year became the butt of jokes and hoaxes and were called April fools.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78259469</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78259469]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 11:29:09+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 15:23:57+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/20210401-khda-tweet_1788d2b21b1_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/KHDA_1788c6c100d_original-ratio.jpg">
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Government]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Government]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[dbf0666b-092c-4fbb-98a4-d5ac1c5d2843]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Government|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|government|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Spreading rumours on ‘April Fool’s Day’ in UAE can land you in prison, State Prosecutor’s Office warns]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Spreading rumours on ‘April Fool’s Day’ in UAE can land you in prison, State Prosecutor’s Office warns]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[April Fool’s pranks in UAE can lead to imprisonment for no less than one year]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/government/spreading-rumours-on-april-fools-day-in-uae-can-land-you-in-prison-state-prosecutors-office-warns-1.78261023</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Aghaddir Ali, Senior Reporter]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[UAE State Prosecutor warns against April Fool’s pranks]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Sharjah: The State Prosecutor’s Office has warned residents and visitors through its accounts on social media about the legal consequences of spreading false rumours and playing pranks that harm society in light of what is known as “April Fool”.</p><a href="https://twitter.com/wamnews/status/1377536378817380352?s=20" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>

<p>The UAE Public Prosecution has indicated that rumours that negatively affect society, harm public interests, spread negative spirit and disturb public security, and indulging in any such activity is a crime that is punishable by law in the UAE by imprisonment for a period of no less than one year. This applies to anyone who intentionally broadcasts false or malicious news, data, rumours or broadcasts propaganda if such exercise is deemed liable to disturb public security, instil terror among the people or harm public interest in any way.</p><div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read more</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/government/mohamed-bin-zayed-saudi-crown-prince-discuss-green-middle-east-initiative-1.1617056104286">Mohamed bin Zayed, Saudi Crown Prince discuss 'Green Middle East’ initiative
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/government/sheikh-mohammed-congratulates-nations-leadership-for-uaes-top-ranking-in-arab-world-in-gender-gap-report-1.78259123">Sheikh Mohammed congratulates nation’s leadership for UAE’s top ranking in Arab world in gender gap report
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/government/smart-police-station-at-dubai-silicon-oasis-to-facilitate-services-1.78235526">Smart Police Station at Dubai Silicon Oasis to facilitate services
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/government/uae-launches-first-gccs-action-plan-on-women-peace-security-1.78211761">UAE launches first GCC’s Action Plan on Women, Peace, Security
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<p>Public Prosecution further warned that all such instances of breach of law will be dealt with in accordance with Article 198 of the Federal Penal Code of the UAE.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78261023</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78261023]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 13:11:56+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 13:25:20+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/08/06/court--law--judgement_16c66d52d6e_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/08/06/court--law--judgement_16c66d52d6e_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[An expat was stabbed in Dubai during a heated argument.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[UAE]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[UAE]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[42e7affe-0f39-4cd5-bb8d-2b673fb6c993]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Dubai Police arrest a French drug lord known as ‘the Ghost’]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Dubai Police arrest a French drug lord known as ‘the Ghost’]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Bouchinbi has been on the run for the last 10 years travelling under false identity]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/dubai-police-arrest-a-french-drug-lord-known-as-the-ghost-1.78262986</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Update]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Ali Al Shouk, Senior Reporter]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Video: French drug lord ‘the Ghost’ arrested in Dubai ]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Dubai: Dubai Police arrested a French drug lord known as ‘the Ghost’ who was wanted over drug trafficking and smuggling operations in Europe.</p>
<p>Moufide Bouchibi, the 39-year-old international kingpin, has been on the run for 10 years after travelling under false identify.</p><a href="https://vimeo.com/531726055/206f4617fa" data-embed class="social-embed"></a><figcaption class="image-caption" itemprop="description">This is how Dubai Police arrest French drug lord 'th Ghost'.<span class="image-credit">Dubai Police</span></figcaption>
<p>Dubai Police succeeded in arresting him depsite the fact the only photo they have was taken 20-year ago. The French drug lord became a global trafficker, smuggling between 50 to 60 tonnes of cannabis to Europe every year with an estimated annual value of €70 million (Dh302 million).</p>
<p>According to Dubai Police, the arrest came after a red arrest warrant was issued in 2021 as Moufide also nown as‘Mouf’ entered the UAE impersonating another person with official travel documents.</p><div class="mugshot-block">
<div class="author-square float-right ">
<img class="author-image square" src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/04/14/Lieutenant-General-Abdullah-Khalifa-Al-Marri_171784828f3_author.jpg">

    <div class="author">Lieutenant General Abdullah Khalifa Al Marri</div>
</div>
    <p>
        <span>Lieutenant General Abdullah Khalifa Al Marri, Commander-in-Chief of Dubai Police, said the arrest is another achievement to the fruitful cooperation between Dubai Police and international law enforcement agencies towards ensuring the world’s security and safety.</span>
    </p>
</div>

<p>Major General Khalil Ibrahim Al Mansouri, Assistant Commander-in-Chief for Criminal Investigation Affairs at Dubai Police, said a team of elite officers was assigned to the task.</p>
<p>“After exchanging information with the French authorities concerned, the Data Analysis Centre at Dubai Police located the drug lord and monitored his movement until he was arrested,” Maj Gen Al Mansouri said.</p><div class="mugshot-block">
<div class="author-square float-right ">
<img class="author-image square" src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/08/23/190823-Major-General-Expert-Khalil-Ibrahim-Al-Mansouri-2_16cbe819ca7_author.jpg">

    <div class="author">Major General Khalil Ibrahim Al Mansouri</div>
</div>
    <p>
        <span>“After exchanging information with the French authorities concerned, the Data Analysis Centre at Dubai Police located the drug lord and monitored his movement until he was arrested,” Maj Gen Al Mansouri said.</span>
    </p>
</div>

<h3>10-years of escape</h3>
<p>Brigadier Jamal Salem Al Jallaf, director of the Criminal Investigation Department at Dubai Police, said ‘Mouf’ became a global drug trafficker and was wanted for ten-year.</p><div class="mugshot-block">
<div class="author-square float-right ">
<img class="author-image square" src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/06/09/Brigadier-Jamal-Al-Salem-Al-Jallaf_16b3ce8a816_author.jpg">

    <div class="author">Brigadier Jamal Salem Al Jallaf</div>
</div>
    <p>
        <span>“In 2015, the Bordeaux Court sentenced Bouchibi to 20 years. For many years, he remained on the run and managed to escape arrest. French detectives had only a photo of him taken 20-year-ago,” Brig Al Jallaf said. Dubai Police were able to identify Mouf’s location by analysing available data, pictures and videos.</span>
    </p>
</div>

<p>According to Dubai Police, ‘Mouf’ was using flase identities and had not made a single transaction or purchase under his real name since his arrival to Dubai. “He was like the invisible man which was a big challenge for our teams,” Brig Al Jallaf said. However, Dubai Police did not reveal when ‘Mouf’ had arrived to the country. “As soon as our officers conclude the investigation, Bouchibi will be referred to the Public Prosecution for extradition.</p>
<h3>International praise for Dubai</h3>
<p>Jérôme Bonet, Central Director of the French Judiciary Police, lauded Dubai Police’s commitment to the fight against international drug trafficking and organised crime.</p>
<p>He praised the close cooperation between the French Anti-Narcotics Agency (OFAST) and the Dubai Police that led to the arrest of Bouchibi.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78262986</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78262986]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 15:14:54+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 16:22:23+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/09/10/190910-dubai-police_16d1b98ebfe_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/09/10/190910-dubai-police_16d1b98ebfe_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Dubai Police have issued fines to an expat woman for holding house party in violation of COVID-19 protocol. Photo for illustrative purpose only.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Business]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Business]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[5344044f-f9bd-406a-ab6d-16919b12a93d]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Business|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[reachArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|business|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[How to trade pharmaceutical stocks via CFDs]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[How to trade pharmaceutical stocks via CFDs]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Stocks in the industry have seen a significant increase in trading volumes due to COVID-19]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/business/how-to-trade-pharmaceutical-stocks-via-cfds-1.1617184858862</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Partner Content]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Daniel Takieddine, Senior Market Analyst & Head Of Sales – FXPRIMUS]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[How to trade pharmaceutical stocks via CFDs]]></linktext>
		<sponsorLogo><![CDATA[https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/FXPrimus-logo_17887b77981_logo.jpg]]></sponsorLogo>
		<sponsorText><![CDATA[Sponsored by]]></sponsorText>
		<sponsorName><![CDATA[FXPRIMUS]]></sponsorName>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Contracts for difference (CFDs) is a form of derivatives trading that allows investors to trade based on prices acquired from an underlying market instead of the market itself. Pharmaceutical stocks CFDs trading has in recent months, for obvious&nbsp;reasons, become especially popular.</p>
<p>In today’s unprecedented times, trading volumes for pharmaceutical stocks have seen an increase because companies in these industries are on the frontline of finding a solution for the highly infectious virus COVID-19. A firm that can produce a viable cure for the virus will immediately see a surge in its stock price, and several companies have already benefited from that.</p>
<h3>How have the stocks been performing?</h3>
<p>With vaccines now being rolled out, several top pharmaceutical companies have seen significant improvements in their share price. Over the past six months, Pfizer’s (PFE) stock rose from $34.27 after the company confirmed that it had been seeing significant results in trials for its coronavirus vaccine. The stock hit a high of $42.56 on December 8, but it has been trading at yearly lows entering 2021.</p>
<p>Primarily, Pfizer’s dwindling performance came from the company’s Q4 2020 reports in February. With the pharmaceutical giant reporting earnings of $11.7 billion, beating analysts’ estimates. However, GAAP earnings of $0.10 per share lagged. Problems with vaccine rollouts have also hit the stock hard.</p>
<p>One company that seems to be doing well, however, is Moderna (MRNA). Over the past six months, its stock price has jumped from $54.34, hitting a high of $185.98 on February 8. While the price has dropped significantly since then, it is still holding strong at $132.19 at the time of writing this report.</p>
<p>All in all, pharma stocks have been putting up some impressive numbers of late. So, why will you want to trade CFDs based on these stocks?</p><blockquote>
    <h2 class="card-title">
        <span>A CFD trade is an agreement to exchange the difference between the opening and closing price of your asset. Thanks to this structure, these instruments offer more flexibility than some other investment solutions.</span>
    </h2>

    <div class="author">Daniel Takieddine, Senior Market Analyst & Head Of Sales – FXPRIMUS</div>
</blockquote>
<h3>Access to leverage</h3>
<p>When investing in these stocks via CFD contracts, one can amplify the volume being traded using leverage. This means leverage lets you trade with more than the deposit you have put in your trading account. That deposit is known as margin.</p>
<p>When you put down the margin and set a leverage level, you can trade with more money than you have got. From there, any profits and losses you make will be based on your leverage - not your margin. Essentially, CFDs provide an opportunity for you to increase your profits however it also works the other way around and losses will also be amplified.</p>
<h3>Optimal trade flexibility</h3>
<p>A CFD trade is an agreement to exchange the difference between the opening and closing price of your asset. Thanks to this structure, these instruments offer more flexibility than some other investment solutions. You can trade in pharmaceutical sectors that are showing a downward trend in price, as well as those looking up.</p>
<p>When you trade CFDs, you see the opening and closing price of your position. You can trade at the buy price if you think the pharma stocks will jump, and you can select the price at which you would like to sell at if you think they will slump. With the industry currently receiving a lot of attention, CFDs provide an opportunity for you to trade on market news announcements with a certain level of flexibility.</p>
<h3>Effective share portfolio hedging</h3>
<p>So, imagine you own several shares of MRNA, and you are looking to keep those shares for a long period of time. But now let’s say a new vaccine has been discovered by a new pharmaceutical company. You may believe that certain stocks linked to the industry will drop in value, and thus you look to offset potential losses on your MRNS stock. With CFDs, you could open a short position and do just that.</p>
<p>If you turn out to be right and MRNA - or the entire pharma industry - slumps, you will make a profit on your CFD short position. If the shares increase in value, you can quickly close your short position and offset the losses you incur in the future.</p>
<p>As you can see there are many advantages to trading pharmaceutical stocks and it’s an exciting time to get involved in these fast-moving asset classes. At FXPRIMUS we offer direct market access to these stocks via demo (practice) and live trading accounts. We also provide a range of educational material in English and Arabic to help you get started.</p>
<p><em>To learn more visit <a href="https://www.fxprimus.com/int/" target="_blank">www.fxprimus.com</a></em></p>
<p><em>“Any opinions, news, research, analyses, prices or other information contained here are provided as general market commentary and do not constitute investment advice. FXPRIMUS does not accept liability for any loss or damage, including without limitation to, any loss of proﬁt, which may arise directly or indirectly from the use of or reliance on such information.”</em></p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617184858862</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617184858862]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 07:00:37+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 07:01:00+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/FXPrimus_17887b630f9_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/FXPrimus_17887b630f9_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Daniel Takieddine, Senior Market Analyst & Head Of Sales – FXPRIMUS]]></media:title>
			<media:description type="plain"><![CDATA[FXPRIMUS]]></media:description>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Health]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Health]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[7469ee64-6633-4a26-b780-76b3c85d7856]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Health|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|health|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[COVID-19: UAE reports 2,315 new coronavirus cases, 2 deaths]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[COVID-19: UAE reports 2,315 new coronavirus cases, 2 deaths]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[The updated numbers were confirmed on Thursday]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/health/covid-19-uae-reports-2315-new-coronavirus-cases-2-deaths-1.1617262779445</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Update]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Gulf News Report]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[UAE reports 2,315 new coronavirus cases, 2 deaths]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Dubai: UAE reported 2,315 new coronavirus cases on Thursday.</p>
<p>The Ministry of Health and Prevention also reported two fatalities, taking the death toll of the disease to 1,499.</p>
<p>The Ministry of Health conducted 237,240 tests over a 24-hour period, leading to the discovery of those infected. The total number of tests conducted in the UAE since the pandemic began stands at&nbsp;37,836,288; the total number of infections detected is at 463,759.</p>
<p>2,435 recoveries were also confirmed, taking the total number of people who have recovered to 447,790.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617262779445</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617262779445]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 13:53:52+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 14:02:01+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/01/15/20210115-coronavirus-cases_1770591a305_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/01/15/20210115-coronavirus-cases_1770591a305_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[The latest coronavirus patients were identified after conducting more than 131,262 additional COVID-19 tests among UAE citizens and residents over the past few days.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Op-Eds]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Op-Eds]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[415987d9-185d-4e9c-b629-64cc709800dd]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Op-Eds|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|opinion|op-eds|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Sharad Pawar talking to Modi-Shah from position of weakness]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Sharad Pawar talking to Modi-Shah from position of weakness]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Maratha leader allegedly met with Amit Shah amid high political drama in Maharashtra]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/opinion/op-eds/sharad-pawar-talking-to-modi-shah-from-position-of-weakness-1.78240640</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Political instinct]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Sheela Bhatt, Special to Gulf News]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Pawar talking to Modi-Shah from position of weakness]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>In a matter of only 16 months, Sharad Pawar, who used to talk to Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Home Minister Amit Shah from a position of strength in November 2019, is now looking for “protection” of his party man Anil Deshmukh, the Home minister of Maharashtra.</p>
<p>Mumbai’s recently transferred Police Commissioner, Param Bir Singh, in his letter to Chief Minister, Uddhav Thackeray, made a sensational claim that Deshmukh had directed suspended assistant police commissioner Sachin Waze to collect Rs100 crore every month for him — from bars restaurants and other establishments.</p>
<p>Singh himself doesn’t enjoy too much credibility but his letter is potent enough to invite legal repercussions. Never before has any Home minister has been directly accused in this manner of running an extortion racket.</p>
<h3>Uncomfortable allies</h3>
<p>Thus far, publicly Pawar and his party supported Deshmukh but this has left the allies uncomfortable. Congress’s leader and former Maharastra Chief Minister Prithviraj Chavan told<em> Gulf News</em>, “There is a moral issue involved in the letter but we are waiting for the inquiry to come out.”</p>
<p>Singh’s acutely embarrassing allegations has made Pawar uneasy because he himself had selected pliable Deshmukh to run the ministry. Pawar, who was hospitalised recently, is one of the wiliest politicians independent India has seen. He has mastered the art of keeping all vested interests on his side. Modi and Shah are late entrants in the game.</p>
<p>Also, the arrest of Sachin Vaze by the NIA has created some tension, if not scare in the state government. Nobody knows how much Vaze knows and what all he will share with the central agency.</p>
<p>Vaze, who had joined Shiv Sena during the years when he was suspended, has been arrested in connection with an explosives laden vehicle that was found near the home of billionaire industralist Mukesh Ambani.</p>
<p>Vaze’s arrest, death of an eyewitness, phone-tapping by the sleuth in police department and Singh’s letter has affected the Maharashtra government, politically.</p>
<p>Reportedly, Vaze and his top boss Singh were actually working in tandem which makes situation more complicated.</p>
<h3>Flight to Ahmedabad</h3>
<p>Obviously, Pawar must have felt the heat of the situation. In less than a week after Singh’s damaging letter became public, he flew to Ahmedabad.</p>
<p>On Friday 26, March Pawar arrived in Ahmedabad from Mumbai along with his longtime friend and the party leader Praful Patel. Around the same time home minister Amit Shah also arrived in Ahmedabad from Delhi.</p>
<p>However, sources in the establishment leaked the news on Twitter, giving indication of the presence of both top-level leaders in an informal set up near Thaltej highway.</p>
<p>While Shah didn’t clearly deny meeting Pawar, Mumbai pulsated. Even Sanjay Raut, Sena leader, acknowledged the alleged Pawar-Shah meeting initially but later denied it.</p>
<p>The “leaked news”, fake or real, may have implications on the Maharashtra government that’s run by Maha Vikas Aghadi of Shiv Sena, NCP and Congress. The Aghadi was created to stop BJP from forming the government in Maharashtra.</p>
<p>The BJP had done well in elections in October 2019 but its old ally Shiv Sena wanted the top post of chief minister. The tussle that followed got sour between Uddhav Thackeray and Shah.</p>
<p>BJP and NCP could have joined hands and given a stable government, but Modi and Shah got the jolt when Pawar in November 2019 meeting -- in Modi’s office in parliament -- decided not to opt for the political alliance with BJP.</p>
<p>Pawar calculated he might wield total power, more freedom with a regional party — Shiv Sena — and a weakened and divided state Congress. The unthinkable happened when “secular Congress” supported Shiv Sena.</p>
<p>It was a classic ‘Pawar moment’ when Uddhav Thakerey was sworn-in under the game plan, prepared and executed well by Pawar. Modi and Shah were checkmated in spite of their best efforts.</p>
<p>Now, in less than two years, Shiv Sena and Congress are having reality check. While Uddhav started off quite well, lately his party is struggling to maintain its strong Hindutva identity and is facing severe and multiple after-effects of Covid while administrating the state.</p>
<p>The thinking in Congress is that apart from their common goal of keeping the Maratha network strong, there is nothing much to gain if the NCP dominates the show, the way it is doing now. Sena and the Congress both find the NCP consolidating ground at their cost but none of three allies are ready to rock the boat, yet.</p>
<p>There is also fear that the BJP is as strong as it was in November 2019. The NCP can grow at expense of the Congress and BJP can grow at expense of Sena but it seems the BJP is treading slowly.</p>
<h3>Mentor of Marathas</h3>
<p>BJP is acutely aware that Pawar is 80 and has an image of being the mentor of the Marathas. Since the last few elections, the BJP has gained among the OBC minus Marathas but Devendra Fadnavis has been unable to build up personal credentials among the Maratha voters.</p>
<p>The BJP is unlikely to do any political manoeuvring that may hurt Maratha pride. It will be satisfied, for time being, if the ruling parties stand divided over the issues ignited by the BJP.</p>
<p>Pawar, on the other hand, is the leader in hurry. He has been nurturing national ambitions since decades, but failed.</p>
<p>Raut has started batting for Pawar saying the Maratha strongman should be made chief of UPA by replacing Sonia Gandhi to take on Modi. This has upset Congress. Maharastra state chief, Nana Patole, has snubbed Raut strongly. In Kerala election, Pawar’s party has aligned with the Left front and fighting against the Congress.</p>
<p>Pawar’s current predicament is understandable.</p>
<p>In national politics May 2 is emerging as the crucial date when the assembly results of West Bengal and other four states would be out.</p>
<p>Mamata Bannerji’s victory or loss both are not going to be of much help to Pawar’s national ambitions.</p>
<p>If, Mamata Bannerji loses the state, the BJP would gain enormous heft and supreme confidence. Modi-Shah will become hard negotiators at all levels in all the states.</p>
<p>BJP will get hyper in Maharashtra where it’s the largest party. Some Congress MLAs and a section of Shiv Sena have lost interest in the current dispensation and might negotiate their future with the BJP if the saffron outfit wins the difficult state of West Bengal.</p>
<p>If Mamata wins, not just Pawar even Rahul will feel the Mamata challenge in taking the leadership role against Modi.</p>
<p>The issue before Pawar is that after May 2, he will have to completely redraw all his plans that helped him stand up against Modi-Shah in November 2019.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78240640</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78240640]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-03-31 09:20:56+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 09:26:52+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Pawar-Amit-Shah_1788be55ede_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Pawar-Amit-Shah_1788be55ede_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[The purported high profile meeting between Sharad Pawar and Aamit Shah took place last week amid a political crisis in Maharashtra ]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[entertainment-photos]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[entertainment-photos]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[66f4df86-1515-4469-af32-a3846fcf6b0c]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[entertainment-photos|BollyWood|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[galleryArticle]]></articleType>
		<department><![CDATA[blank|photos|entertainment|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Bollywood: 'Bigg Boss 6' contestant Sana Khan sips gold-plated coffee in Dubai's Burj Khalifa 
]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Bollywood: 'Bigg Boss 6' contestant Sana Khan sips gold-plated coffee in Dubai's Burj Khalifa 
]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[She posted photos from the highest restaurant in the world - Atmosphere ]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/photos/entertainment/bollywood-bigg-boss-6-contestant-sana-khan-sips-gold-plated-coffee-in-dubais-burj-khalifa-1.1617248319588</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Nilanjana G. Javed]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Sana Khan sips gold-plated coffee in Burj Khalifa]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617248319588</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617248319588]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 07:23:57+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 10:17:27+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-teaser_1788baf0d0d_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
				<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan-_1788b81c896_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Former actor Sana Khan enjoying the bliss of her newly married, was spotted on a breakfast date with her husband, Anas Saiyyad, in Dubai, giving major couple goals.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/Saiyad Sana Khan]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788b8478e3_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[The actress, who was a part of the film fraternity for over a decade before giving it up, was seen sipping on gold-plated coffee at Burj Khalifa’s At.Mosphere.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/sanakhaan21 ]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788b863c0d_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[She posted a photo from the world's highest restaurant: "When ur husband suprise’s u with breakfast at the top of the BURJ KHALIFA That gold plated coffee (sic)."]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/sanakhaan21 ]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788b8790a9_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[She posted a selfie with her husband too. She announced her retirement from acting in October last year, with a note expressing her wish to spend her life in the service of humanity and following the orders of her ‘creator’. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/Saiyad Sana Khan]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788ba16a9a_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[At the time, she wrote:. “Today I am talking to you standing at a crucial juncture of my life. For years, I have been living the Showbiz (film industry) life, and during this time I have been blessed with all kinds of fame, honour and wealth from my fans for which I am grateful to them.”]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/sanakhaan21]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788ba52d7d_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[After tying the knot, Sana flew to Kashmir for her honeymoon. She shared videos from the Dal Lake, the Hazratbal Shrine and from her hotel room to give a glimpse of the picturesque location.  ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/sanakhaan21]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/12/21/Sana-Khan_17685377209_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Sana enjoyed her honeymoon in Kashmir, here she is playing with snow.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Sana-Khan_1788b9bcd54_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Sana Khan is a former Indian actress, model and dancer.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Insta/sanakhaan21 ]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[entertainment-photos]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[entertainment-photos]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[66f4df86-1515-4469-af32-a3846fcf6b0c]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[entertainment-photos|Entertainment|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[galleryArticle]]></articleType>
		<department><![CDATA[blank|photos|entertainment|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Weekend watchlist: 10 TV shows and movies to check out
]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Weekend watchlist: 10 TV shows and movies to check out
]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA['Wild Dog', 'Nomadland', 'Kingdom' and other recommendations to enjoy this weekend]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/photos/entertainment/weekend-watchlist-10-tv-shows-and-movies-to-check-out-1.1617270238184</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Jennifer Barretto]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Weekend watchlist: 10 TV shows and movies to check out]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617270238184</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617270238184]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 13:32:11+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 13:50:05+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/Nagarjuna-in--Wild-Dogs-_178881a1069_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
				<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/A-still-from-Wild-Dog_17888411c9b_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Wild Dog (UAE cinemas): South Indian superstar Nagarjuna will wage a war on terror in his latest action thriller ‘Wild Dog’. In the movie directed by Ahishor Solomon, Nagarjuna will play the fictional head of India’s counter-terrorist task force National Investigation Agency (NIA), which is trying to find the people behind the twin blasts in Hyderabad in 2013. The film is based on real events and will re-create the anti-terror squad’s investigations leading up to the arrest of the criminals responsible for the Dilsukhnagar explosions that killed dozens and injured many others. There’s plenty of action in this anti-terrorist procedural.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Anugraheethan-Antony_1788ccbf355_original-ratio.JPG">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Anugraheethan Antony (UAE cinemas): Starring Sunny Wayne, Suraj Venjaramood and Gouri Kishan, this Malayalam-language feature is mix of drama, romance and fantasy. “There’s a bit of everything. It’s a film that gives importance to love, music and relationships of various nature … Also, this role is different from the roles that I have done before … The audience will really enjoy the characters and the unique plot,” said Wayne in an interview with Gulf News in Malayalam.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/02/19/tab-Anupam-Kher-in--New-Amsterdam--1550570620106_16a4a1643e7_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[New Amsterdam (Netflix): If you combine the melodrama and romance of ‘Grey’s Anatomy’ with the investigative science of ‘House’, what you get is the highly addictive series ‘New Amsterdam’. The medical drama, based on the book ‘Twelve Patients: Life and Death at Bellevue Hospital’ by Eric Manheimer, stars Ryan Eggold as medical director Dr Max Godwin who brings revolutionary changes to an outdated hospital. It also stars Bollywood actor Anupam Kher.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/16/TAB-Sandeep-Aur-Pinky-Faraar--3--1615889344731_1783a82a8db_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Pinky Aur Sandeep Faraar (UAE cinemas): If you haven’t had the chance to catch Arjun Kapoor and Parineeti Chopra’s slow-burn black comedy yet, it isn’t too late. ‘PASF’ is still playing in the UAE cinemas. Director Dibakar Banerjee’s engaging drama transports you into the lives of two people who belong to two disparate worlds and are forced to flee for survival. Sandeep (Parineeti Chopra) belongs to the upper crust banking world, while her reluctant running mate Pinky (Arjun Kapoor), represents the lower rung of a deeply divided India with glaring economic and class inequalities. He’s uncouth and unlikeable at first, while she’s sophisticated on the outside with a shady back story. The movie explores the dark side of greed and desire. This film is a compelling one-time watch powered by strong performances.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/10/01/Peaky-Blinders1-1569936820293_16d8786c845_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Peaky Blinders (Netflix): Keep busy the whole weekend with five seasons of this popular award-winning show that stars Cillian Murphy in the lead. The crime drama set in Birmingham, England, follows the exploits of Tommy Shelby (Murphy) and his crime family after the First World War. It first aired in 2013 and went on to gain massive popularity around the world. The show won a Bafta TV award for best drama series in 2018.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/04/Parineeti-Chopra-as-Saina-Nehwal_177fd549b2e_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Saina (UAE cinemas): In the mood for an inspiring biopic? Bollywood actress Parineeti Chopra channels her energies into bringing the life and times of ace badminton player Saina Nehwal to the big screen. While the sports biopic is not subtle, it has a few high points. Written by director Amol Gupte, Chopra goes about smashing patriarchy and gender divides, one good match at a time.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[YOUTUBE]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/10/29/modern-love-MOLV-S106-1811-SACH-0109RC2-rgb-1572353403355_16e1790e9db_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Modern Love (Amazon Prime Video): Indulge in an escape from reality with this romantic show. The anthology romcom series first released in 2019 and it’s based on the New York Times column of the same name. It explores various love stories set in New York City. There’s also a podcast where actors read the columns. Season one of ‘Modern Love’ featured actors such as Anne Hathaway, Tina Fey, John Slattery and Dev Patel, and season two is on the way.]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/22/Copy-of-TAB-Nomadland-1-1616395572802_17858af1645_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Nomadland (UAE cinemas): This is your chance to watch a film that has been highly praised by critics and has won Golden Globes for Best Motion Picture – Drama and Best Director for Chloe Zhao. In it, Frances McDormand plays woman in her 60s who loses everything in the Great Recession. Wanting to escape from her reality, she sells all her belongings and buys a van so she can travel as a nomad through the American West. This moving drama also earned six nominations at the 93rd Academy Awards.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[AP]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Actor-Mammootty-in--The-One-_1788cd6ad70_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[The One (UAE cinemas): With the elections in Kerala, this film is topical. Malayalam superstar Mammootty leads this political thriller, directed by Santosh Viswanathan, to the finish line. The superstar plays the head of state, Kerala Chief Minister Kadakkal Chandran, an ideal public servant who is keen to clean out the rot and corruption in his political landscape. If you love Mammootty’s bombastic style of acting, then you can put your money down on this one.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[facebook.com/Mammootty]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/TV-show-Kingdom-_1788cd469c1_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Kingdom (Netflix): If zombie movies and shows are your thing, then this South Korean series is a must-watch. Strange rumours about the ill king grip a kingdom that has been struck by famine and corruption. The crown prince then becomes the kingdom’s only hope even as a mysterious plague overtakes the land.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Netflix]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Technology]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Technology]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[2cdb03c9-93c2-445e-98f5-a94fa30fe233]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[reachArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>video</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|technology|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G equips content creators with features to express themselves better]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G equips content creators with features to express themselves better]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G’s camera is the ultimate tool for content creation in any situation]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/technology/oppo-reno-5-pro-5g-equips-content-creators-with-features-to-express-themselves-better-1.1617024192308</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Partner Content]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Vaibhav Pradip | GN Reach]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G is perfect for you]]></linktext>
		<sponsorLogo><![CDATA[https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2019/04/30/Oppo-Logo_16a6f147626_logo.png]]></sponsorLogo>
		<sponsorText><![CDATA[In association with]]></sponsorText>
		<sponsorName><![CDATA[Oppo]]></sponsorName>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>The all-5G Oppo Reno 5 Series brings industry-leading photography and videography features in your hand. With its flagship Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G smartphone, you can create endless fun content. It features a range of powerful AI camera functions for any situation, a stunning design and a competitive price which in combination offers a truly versatile and future-proof experience.</p>
<h2>Capturing memories is easier than ever</h2>
<p>Co-developed between Oppo and Sony, there is an IMX766 image sensor on the Reno 5 Pro 5G. Its primary lens among the quad-camera array is a 50MP 1/1.56-inch large sensor to take in more light. On top of the hardware, Reno 5 Pro 5G comes with a powerful range of AI-assisted features called AI Highlight Video.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/29/Oppo-Reno-5-Pro-5G-1-_1787eb24b7d_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Supplied</span></figcaption>
<p>This is especially useful for vlogging when you are out and about. For example, when capturing the Dubai Water Canal in the evening, the smartphone can use the Ultra Night Video algorithm to optimize video quality for a bright, sharp and natural look. To capture portraits with a sunset backdrop, it uses the Live HDR algorithm. This helps you capture perfectly exposed subjects with a background that has natural colors and fine details. You can use this feature on both the front and rear cameras of Reno 5 Pro 5G giving content creators added freedom.</p>
<p>In fast paced videos and cinematics, Oppo’s Focus Tracking and Ultra Steady Video 3.0 are useful. With Focus Tracking, Reno 5 Pro 5G recognizes faces, pets and other common video subjects to automatically lock and track focus. There is an in-built AI-based movement predictor on the smartphone which helps subjects stay in focus. To tackle movement further, Ultra Steady Video 3.0 allows you to take stable and high-quality videos amidst the hustle and bustle of city life.</p>
<p>Even avid photographers can benefit from Reno 5 Pro 5G’s capabilities. When you quickly want to capture a specific moment, Flash Snapshot allows the camera to start to focus on a subject the moment it is opened. Of course, additional features include Night Flare Portrait, an Ultra Dark Mode, AI Scene Enhancement capable of recognizing 22 different scenes and Ultra Night Selfie Mode using the smartphone’s 32MP front camera.</p>
<h2>Never run out of power</h2>
<p>Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G comes with a 6.5-inch 3D curved Super AMOLED display. Its 90Hz refresh rate and 180Hz touch sampling rate makes everything on the screen feel smooth. The 2,400 x 1,080 resolution FHD+ panel is also HDR10+ certified which means colors in movies will look rich and vibrant.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/29/Oppo-Reno-5-Pro-5G-2-_1787eb36009_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Supplied</span></figcaption>
<p>Inside, you find a 4,500mAh large battery with 65W SuperVOOC 2.0 Flash Charge. This gives you a full charge up to 100 per-cent in just 35 minutes, making overnight charging a thing of the past. For solid performance, the smartphone packs Qualcomm’s Snapdragon 865 processor coupled with 12GB of RAM and 256GB of ROM. The 7nm SoC features a multi-cooling system that allows you to play your favorite games for hours on end. You can take advantage of multi-window support and an optimized dark more with Oppo’s ColorOS 11.1 on Reno 5 Pro 5G to further customize the experience.</p>
<p>To ensure the best connectivity on the go, the native 5G performance of the Snapdragon 865 processor is improved further with Oppo’s 5G + WiFi Dual Channel Acceleration and 360-degree surround antenna design. Both in combination ensure a fast, stable and more consistent 5G experience.</p>
<h2>Easy to carry everywhere</h2>
<p>At just 7.99mm and 184g, Oppo Reno 5 Pro 5G is exceptionally thin and light for a 5G smartphone. Its new Reno Glow appearance gives it a colorful look and a satisfying touch which keeps the smartphone scratch, smudge and fingerprint resistant. The glowing finish is a result of Oppo’s new pyramid structure used on the back of the smartphone.</p>
<h2>Pricing and availability</h2>
<p>Oppo’s all-5G Reno 5 Series is currently available in the UAE at a retail price of Dh2,799 for Reno 5 Pro 5G and Dh1,999 for Reno 5 5G. Oppo Reno 5 Z 5G is currently on pre-order for Dh1,499.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617024192308</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617024192308]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-03-30 07:00:54+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-03-30 07:01:01+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/29/Reno-5_1787eb4952a_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
				<media:content url="https://vimeo.com/530297147" type="video/quicktime" medium="video">
			<media:keywords><![CDATA[Technology|]]></media:keywords>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Parenting-Learning-Play]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Parenting-Learning-Play]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[26e19b8b-4c7f-4949-be73-b43a92c4f194]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Parenting-Learning-Play|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[galleryArticle]]></articleType>
		<department><![CDATA[blank|parenting|learning-play|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Easter Dubai 2021: Events and family activities in the UAE this Easter]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Easter Dubai 2021: Events and family activities in the UAE this Easter]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[From egg hunts to bunny meets and afternoon teas, kids will love these Easter treats]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/parenting/learning-play/easter-dubai-2021-events-and-family-activities-in-the-uae-this-easter-1.1617254481989</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Sangeetha Sagar]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[17 Egg-citing Easter events for families in the UAE ]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617254481989</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617254481989]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 07:13:52+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 10:02:38+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Easter-kids_1788be0e067_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
				<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Easter-kids_1788be0e067_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[ Celebrate Easter in the UAE this weekend with egg hunts, bunny meets and of course lots and lots of Easter treats that both big and little kids are sure to love…]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/07/27/Staycation_UAE_Mandarin-Oriental-Dubai_1738f1f9710_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[MANDARIN ORIENTAL JUMEIRA’S EASTER BY THE SEA: Celebrate by the sea at Mandarin Oriental’s The Bay with an Easter-themed buffet on Friday April 2 with a range of specials for all ages and taste buds. The stunning terrace overlooking the beach and a unique brasserie-style atmosphere is sure to please the parents, and while you feast on a huge selection of Mediterranean favourites and refreshing drinks, the little ones will be enjoying a host of Easter games including an egg trail, bunny hunt, face painting and much more. DETAILS: Prices start from Dh400 per person including soft drinks, Friday April 2, 12:30pm - 4pm. For reservations call 04 777 2233 or email modub-thebay@mohg.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be87267_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[STUDIO ONE’S MAD HATTERS BBQ On Friday April 2, The Void at Studio One Hotel is hosting a wonderland of sorts, and yes, fancy dress is encouraged. While adults enjoy a BBQ and drinks package, little ones can enjoy the kids’ area packed with games and sugary treats. BBQ treats, an Easter candy hunt and cupcake making are all on the list.  DETAILS: From Dh175 for adults with a three-course BBQ menu and soft drinks; Dh50 for kids under seven, free for babies. Friday April 2, 12.30pm to 4pm. Book at thevoid@studioonehotel.com. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be873cc_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[SOFITEL DUBAI THE PALM’S POOL/BEACH DAY OUT: At Sofitel, on Friday April 2 between 2-4pm you can tuck into a lunch buffet with traditional Easter delicacies at either Manava or Porterhouse Steaks & Grills. During lunch the little ones will be entertained with specially designed activities in the garden area, including a dedicated popcorn machine, crafts, painting, face painting - and of course, an egg hunt! If you want to make a day off it, just add pool and beach access for Dh200. There’s 6 pools, a beautiful white sand beach, children’s pools and the fully equipped Amura kids’ club.  DETAILS: Easter Lunch is on Friday, April 2, 1pm to 4pm at Manava or Porterhouse. From Dh375 per adult, Dh225 per teen (12 to 20 years), and Dh115 per child (six to 11 years), including unlimited water, juices and soft beverages. Extra Dh200 per person for pool and beach access. Advance booking required, www.sofiteldubaithepalm.com, 044 55 66 77.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be870cd_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[REFORM SOCIAL & GRILL’S LAKESIDE CELEBRATIONS:  For a casual dining experience and some simple dishes cooked in true British style, head to Reform Social & Grill, The Lakes Dubai. Friday April 2 and Saturday April 3 will see The Great British Garden hosting an activity-packed weekend out on the lawn and lakeside. On Good Friday you can tuck into bites from the British fish and chip shop, a pop-up station that will sit alongside a lamb roast, British curry shop, pie station and summer dessert offering. Meanwhile, throughout the day the kids will be entertained courtesy of appearances from fairy-tale characters and face painting.  DETAILS: The Great British Garden, Friday April 2 and Saturday April 3. Available slots are 11am to 2.30pm, 3pm to 6.30pm and 7pm to late. Price is Dh200 per person for four tokens. One token to be redeemed against each food and/or beverage item. To book call 04 454 2638 or WhatsApp 058 647 8692.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be87482_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[RITZ-CARLTON, DUBAI, JBR’S EASTER BEACH LUNCH  Head to the casual beachside restaurant Palm Grill for some no-shoes fun at the Chill & Grill Easter Lunch. Offering views of Ain Dubai, Palm Grill’s Saturday April 3 lunch features a selection of barbequed specialties such as lamb skewers, baked salmon and a chilled seafood bar. The little ones will be able to bite into freshly prepared Easter delicacies including hot cross buns, praline Easter eggs, bunny macaroons and an ice cream counter. Or opt for a more elegant affair with The Lobby Lounge’s Easter Afternoon Tea, featuring sandwiches, scones and Easter-themed goodies kiddie will love.   DETAILS: Saturday, April 3, 1pm to 4pm, from Dh275 per person including soft beverages. Dh138 for children 6 to 11 years old, and kids under five dine for free. Lobby Lounge Afternoon Tea available now until April 4, 12.30-5pm, Dh195pp including unlimited tea and coffee, or Dh305 including a glass of premium bubbly. For reservations call  04 318 6150 or email dine.dubai@ritzcarlton.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be872ed_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[AJMAN SARAY’S FACE PAINTING AND EGG HUNTING:  Ajman Saray has planned an entire event for the little ones on Saturday April 3 with a Easter egg hunt as well as some face painting fun that will have them hopping around in joy. The hotel’s recreation team will ensure they have oodles of fun and are well taken care of - while you tuck into some deliciousness at Safi Restaurant & Bar, complete with traditional, juicy roasts, grilled meats and seafood alongside crisp salads, cheese wheel pasta and much more.  DETAILS: Easter Family Lunch at Safi Restaurant, Ajman Saray, a Luxury Collection Resort, Ajman is on Saturday April 3, 1pm – 4pm. Prices start from Dh145 per adult for food plus unlimited soft drinks. To book, call 06 714 2222 or email FB.AjmanSaray@luxurycollection.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be86f70_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[THE MEYDAN HOTEL’S EASTER LUNCH AND EGGS MARKET: It’s a double treat for the whole family - The Meydan Hotel has both Easter lunch and an eggs market on offer. On Friday April 2, dig into an Easter-themed buffet lunch at Farriers, with 11 live cooking stations adding sparkle to the festivities. After, take the kids over to Millennium Lounge for some homemade chocolate Easter eggs at the Easter Eggs Market. DETAILS: For lunch, prices start from Dh189 per person, 1pm to 4pm. Easter eggs at Millennium Lounge cost from Dh25, available until Sunday April 4. To book, email meydanrestaurantreservations@meydanhotels.com or call 04 381 3111.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Ski-dubai_1788bf9aba3_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[SKI DUBAI’S EASTER PASS Yes, snow is forecast for Easter in Dubai. At Mall Of The Emirates’ Ski Dubai, the Easter Pass is available for a limited time, bringing along with it access to the Snow Park and amazing rides plus various value-adds. Families can spend the day competing with one another for the Easter Egg Hunts in the Snow and frame the winning moment with Ski Dubai's Easter photo opps. Plus, there’s unlimited Snow Park Rides and a ride of the chairlift on offer. It’s the perfect way for kids to take a break from the heat  - at -4 degrees.  DETAILS: Dh150, valid from April 1 – 4. For more information visit www.skidxb.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be87341_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[BLACK TAP'S BUNNY CRAZYSHAKE  What's Easter without a sugar overload? The popular New York burger and shakes brand Black Tap has brought out a special treat just in time for Easter Sunday - meet the limited-edition Bunny CrazyShake,  a cherry shake with a vanilla-frosted rim, topped with Easter M&M’s, three chocolate Lindt bunnies, whipped cream, Easter sprinkles and of course a cherry on top. If you dine at Black Tap’s Mall of the Emirates and Dubai Mall outlets, get the kids to find an Easter egg hidden inside any of the Crazyshake milkshakes, and you win some amazing prizes, ranging from discount vouchers to complimentary menu items.  DETAILS: The Bunny CrazyShake is available between April 1 to 4, priced at Dh69, across all of Black Tap’s Dubai venues, including Jumeirah Al Naseem, Rixos Premium Dubai JBR, Mall of the Emirates and The Dubai Mall. Limited quantities available. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be86fe2_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[PALAZZO VERSACE DUBAI’S EASTER EGG HUNT STAYCATION: At Palazzo Versace, from Thursday April 1 to Monday April 5 all rooms will be decked out with Easter amenities, chocolate eggs and chocolate bunnies. Plus, in selected rooms or suites, guests have the chance to find a special Easter egg prize – the kids are going to have great fun at this one.  DETAILS: April 1 – April 5 (minimum three-night stay), including breakfast for two adults and two kids below 12 years old, High Tea once during the stay for two adults and two kids below 12 years old, massage for two once during the stay at The SPA, a Dh200 beverage voucher and a Dh150 spa voucher for massages. Prices start from Dh1,260. For reservations, call 04 556 8805 or email dining@palazzoversace.ae.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be87177_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[RIXOS BAB AL BAHR’S ALL-INCLUSIVE STAYCATION   Book a stay at Rixos Bab Al Bahr hotel on the shores of Al Marjan Island in Ras Al Khaimah, and the kids get to celebrate Easter at the Rixy Kids Club, which will host a variety of activities throughout the day – think an Easter Egg Hunt the morning of Sunday April 4, a session of Easter Eggs-ercises, an Easter egg matching game and a bunny bowling session. After, guests can head over to the Avitane Spa, the largest spa in Ras Al Khaimah, to unwind, before heading to an evening of all-inclusive dining options serving up Easter classics. The day doesn’t end there – there’s also musical performances and an enchanting live Alice in Wonderland show to look forward to!  DETAILS: the Easter events are included as part of the room rate. To book call 07 244 4400 or email reservation.rak@rixos.com. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be8729a_original-ratio.jpeg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[SWISSÔTEL AL GHURAIR COOKIE DECORATION AFTERNOON At Yasmine Lounge, Swissôtel Al Ghurair, your kids are in for a treat, and so are you as you tuck into a stylish afternoon tea with the finest blends and a delicious selection of sweet and savoury bites. Meanwhile, your little ones can unleash their creativity decorating Easter cookies. There’s also a specially crafted menu for Easter that includes some tempting treats such as Chocolate Malt Egg Cake and Nest Cupcakes. DETAILS: April 2 to 4, 12pm - 6pm, Dh150 for two adults and two children. To book call 04 293 3000, WhatsApp 058 832 3190 or email foodandbeverage.alghurair@swissotel.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be87074_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[PERRY & BLACKWELDER’S COLORING COMPETITION FOR KIDS Perry & Blackwelder’s in Souk Madinat Jumeirah is hosting a colouring competition for the little ones from April 1-6 for kids aged nine years old and below. The winner of the best Easter coloring will be announced April 6 and will win a big stuffed toy and a meal for the family! For the kids (and adults) with a sweet tooth, there’s also a special Easter dessert on offer, made of a chocolate nest, half a milk chocolate Easter egg filled with vanilla and chocolate ice cream, and mini eggs.   DETAILS: The Nest Egg is priced at Dh42 and is available for 1-6 April. To make a booking, call 800 666 353 or email restaurants@saroodhospitality.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be86e0f_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[LEGOLAND DUBAI’S EGG-CITING ACTIVITIES From April 1 to 10, Legoland is hosting various egg-citing Easter events for the little ones. There’s an egg hunt for all 10 eggs hidden around the park, with some awesome prizes to be won. There’s creativity to be showcased as kids build a Lego flower in Miniland and then add to the awesome Lego Easter Garden Display. There’s moves to be shown in the Lego Friends Dance Workshop, with sessions running daily. There’s even a cupcake decorating session at Café Terrace for a small fee. After all that exhausting fun, kids then eat free at Caesar's Pizza & Pasta buffet. DETAILS: Prices are Dh220 per person when booked online. Visit https://www.legoland.com/dubai/]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be86e8a_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[JA HATTA FORT HOTEL’S ADOPT-A-BUNNY EASTER:  On Sunday April 4, JA Hatta Fort Hotel is hosting Easter family brunch in the picturesque gardens, complete with egg decorating, an egg hunt and food and beverage in the Palm Tree Garden.  The resort is also offering families the chance to adopt a bunny and become a pet parent from afar, while the rabbits remain professionally cared for in their natural mountain habitat in Hatta. You can visit your pet any time and receive personalised updates about the pet from the resort team.  Families can register their interest in a bunny adoption upon arrival and children will be invited to draw a picture of the bunny they wish to adopt and give them an official name. The bunnies will then proudly wear their new name tags. DETAILS: Outdoor Easter Brunch with family activities on Sunday April 4 is from 12-4pm. Prices start from Dh190 with soft drinks. The Adopt a Bunny programme is on the same day, from 4-6pm, and is free of cost (one bunny adoption per family). To find out more call 04 80 99 333 or reservations.hfh@jaresorts.com. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be86cdd_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[BAB AL SHAMS DESERT RESORT’S GARDEN AFTERNOON LUNCH: Easter celebration settings don’t get more perfect than swaying palm trees – on Sunday April 4 Al Forsan Garden at Bab Al Shams Desert Resort offers up an Easter-themed buffet lunch with some stunning views. The menu’s filled with traditional culinary treats including decadent Easter-themed desserts that are sure to be oh-so popular with the little ones. DETAILS: Sunday April 4, 1pm to 4pm, prices start from Dh350 per person inclusive of soft beverages and fresh juices, Dh175 for children aged 6-12 years and Dh90 for children aged 3-5 years. Kids below three years dine for free. To book, call 04 809 6194 or email restaurants@babalshams.com.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kids-easter-_1788be874b8_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[CAESAR’S PALACE EASTER ROAST AND AFTERNOON TEA: On Saturday 3rd April and Sunday 4th April (Easter Day), Gordon Ramsay Hell’s Kitchen will host a traditional Easter roast, featuring an appearance by the Easter bunny himself, as well as a feast of oysters, meats, cheeses and all the traditional roast trimmings (12.30-3.30pm, Dh295 for a roast and dessert or Dh395 for a roast, dessert, and three beverages, both options include beach access). While mum and dad enjoy the food the kids can make the most of Easter-themed face painting, egg-colouring, beach games and an egg hunt at the Empire Kids Club, open for children aged up to 12 years every day over the Easter weekend. Or you can treat the whole family to an Easter-themed Afternoon Tea - available until Sunday 4th April and served at Roman Lounge, it comes with a choice of sandwiches, pastry treats, and fine teas. DETAILS: Call 04 5566466 or email stay@caesarsdubai.ae, caesars.com/dubai.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[UAE]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[UAE]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[42e7affe-0f39-4cd5-bb8d-2b673fb6c993]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|uae|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi residents help one another access free COVID-19 PCR tests in gesture of solidarity]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi residents help one another access free COVID-19 PCR tests in gesture of solidarity]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Free tests offered in emirate as part of Abu Dhabi’s rigorous COVID-19 screening drive]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/abu-dhabi-residents-help-one-another-access-free-covid-19-pcr-tests-in-gesture-of-solidarity-1.78074187</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Samihah Zaman, Senior Reporter]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Residents help each other get free PCR tests]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Abu Dhabi: In an unmistakeable gesture of solidarity amid the COVID-19 pandemic, residents across Abu Dhabi have been helping one another to avail free PCR screenings in their neighbourhoods.</p>
<p>The free tests are conducted on a daily basis as part of Abu Dhabi’s mass screening programme, which was first launched in June 2020 by the health sector regulator, the Department of Health (DoH). Because the tests cover homes and offices in different localities, residents soon took to informing one another of screenings available in their vicinities.</p>
<h3>Social media groups</h3>
<p>Over time, they also began sharing the information on social media groups. On Facebook in particular, the initiative took on a life of its own. In addition to posts on existing community forums, enterprising residents set up dedicated groups to share information about where the tests were currently ongoing.</p>
<p>This has been particularly useful for many, because Abu Dhabi has in place strict regulations regarding COVID-19 screenings. These regulations will have to be adhered to in order to enter the emirate, enter all its schools and many government buildings, and to access many events. Workers in vital sectors and service industries also need to undergo PCR tests every seven days. There are strict penalties in place for those who violate these regulations.</p>
<p>While the tests conducted as part of Abu Dhabi’s widespread screening programme are free for all, a PCR test at a health facility costs at least Dh65 per person, and this is where the Facebook groups come in handy.</p>
<h3>Accessible PCR tests</h3>
<p>“The authorities in Abu Dhabi are doing such a good job of ensuring that residents remain as safe as possible. These mass screenings are a key example of this because they allow even the most cash-strapped people to ensure that they are safe,” Tauhida Ashraf, 32, a sales coordinator from Bangladesh, told Gulf News.</p>
<p>So far, Ashraf has used Facebook groups three times to find testing locations. Each time, she said the process has been quick and easy. Most recently, she needed to get tested after travelling to Dubai, because Abu Dhabi regulations stipulate that anyone continuing to stay on in the emirate after travel must be tested on two specified dates post-arrival — on Days 4 and 8, if a PCR test result was used to enter the emirate; and on Days 3 and 7 if a DPI test was conducted.</p>
<p>“I used a Facebook group to find out where the test was being conducted. A Facebook user had said they were being conducted at a residential building on Muroor Road. So I drove down and soon saw the queue of masked people waiting for their turn. Because women are given priority, it took me just five minutes to get the test done. I had my COVID-19 negative result on Al Hosn app within 24 hours,” Ashraf explained.</p>
<h3>Adhering to the rules</h3>
<p>Carla Reed, 29, another expat from Lebanon, said she had recently become aware of the dedicated COVID-19 testing groups on Facebook.</p>
<p>“I needed to get my Day 4 COVID-19 test after travelling to Dubai. I was going to head to a hospital, but my friend told me there was a way to easily and legally get the test done free of charge. I found a residential building on Airport Road where the tests were being offered, and I was done within minutes,” Reed said.</p>
<p>“I need to get another COVID-19 test on Day 8, and I plan to do it in the same manner,” she added.</p>
<h3>Easy to spot</h3>
<p>It is easy to spot buildings and establishments where COVID-19 screenings are being offered. There is usually a queue of masked residents, each waiting while maintaining adequate social distancing. At the top of the line, a few PPE-clad healthcare professionals have set up a table or two, along with containers carrying medical equipment for the PCR swabs.</p>
<p>Aushesh Kumar, 38, a sales executive from India, said he had availed of the free PCR tests five times till date.</p>
<p>“I believe this is a privilege offered by Abu Dhabi authorities to residents. It not only helps us to make sure we following all COVID-19 testing regulations, but also helps keeps us safe. My job requires that I get tested every seven days, and these free tests have been a boon,” he said.</p>
<p>Abu Dhabi’s mass screening campaign covers a number of localities every single day, and residents are only too happy to share the information with one another.</p>
<h3>Multiple locations</h3>
<p>Freya Jaffar, founder and administrator of popular Facebook community — Abu Dhabi Q&A — said her group sees multiple posts every single day, even though, unlike some of the other groups, it is not dedicated solely to COVID-19 testing info.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/NAT-FILE-PCR-1617254701618_1788be45a32_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Abu Dhabi’s mass screening campaign covers a number of localities every single day, and residents are only too happy to share the information with one another.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Supplied</span></figcaption>
<p>“We have more than 61,000 members, and there are multiple posts detailing locations where free COVID-19 testing is available for the day. A while ago, I simply tacked a permanent and easily visible post at the top of the group where members can add PCR testing location information for others,” she said.</p>
<p>“These free tests are a definite way to encourage testing by the authorities, and they motivate everyone to keep safe,” she added.</p>
<h3>Many reasons for testing</h3>
<p>There are a variety of reasons why residents avail of the tests: Either they are part of the building or establishment marked out for the day’s COVID-19 screening by the authorities, or they need to undertake the tests in keeping with Abu Dhabi’s travel, work and health-related COVID-19 regulations. Others also avail of the free screenings to simply keep safe.</p>
<p>One resident who has not yet been vaccinated against COVID-19 said she had taken free PCR tests on three separate instances, using information about testing locations from a Facebook group. “Each time, I was worried that I had come into contact with a COVID-19 patient, and I got the test done. Fortunately, I was negative each time,” she said.</p><div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read more</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/health/awareness-drive-free-consultations-during-month-long-autism-campaign-in-uae-1.78243159">Awareness drive, free consultations during month-long autism campaign in UAE
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/health/uae-health-ministry-encourages-health-professionals-to-utilise-e-licensing-services-1.78235913">UAE Health Ministry encourages health professionals to utilise E-licensing services
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/health/covid-19-over-83-million-vaccination-doses-given-in-uae-1.1617196395281">COVID-19: Over 8.3 million vaccination doses given in UAE
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/uae/health/16-food-outlets-suspended-in-ajman-for-violating-health-rules-1.78243318">16 food outlets suspended in Ajman for violating health rules
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<p>Mohammad Z, a 64-year-old business owner, said he planned to avail of a free PCR-test soon. “I have been tested twice at my own home, and as a senior resident, I have also been able to avail of two free PCR tests at screening centres in the emirate. This is indeed a blessing for Abu Dhabi residents,” he said.</p>
<p>“Now, I have to undergo a medical procedure soon and my doctor has asked for a PCR test result first. I have known about the free tests that are offered across the capital every day. So I plan to simply get the test done at one of the locations,” Mohammad said.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78074187</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78074187]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 09:25:05+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 12:02:48+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/NAT-FILE-PCR3-1617254704672_1788be46621_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/NAT-FILE-PCR3-1617254704672_1788be46621_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Paramedics collecting the swab samples at a coronavirus drive-through screening station by Dubai Health Authority at Al Nasr Club in Dubai on 9th April 2020. The drive-through facility, with a capacity of more than 250 tests per day, supports efforts to protect the health and safety of the community by giving people an easily accessible centre to test for COVID-19. Photo: Ahmed Ramzan/ Gulf News]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Going-out]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Going-out]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[d621e2ed-3419-4a42-939e-81f38bf3d24c]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Going-out|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[galleryArticle]]></articleType>
		<department><![CDATA[blank|going-out|blank|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[10 exciting ways to spend the weekend in the UAE]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[10 exciting ways to spend the weekend in the UAE]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[We tell you how to make the most out of your weekends in the UAE]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/going-out/10-exciting-ways-to-spend-the-weekend-in-the-uae-1.1617254296987</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Yousra Zaki]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[10 exciting ways to spend the weekend in the UAE]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617254296987</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617254296987]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 10:40:10+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 10:42:39+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/thinsg-to-do-_1788c29881d_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
				<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/thinsg-to-do-_1788c29881d_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[From dragon boat racing, to amazing meal deals for Dubai Food Festival... Beat the boredom with our list of things to do this weekend in the UAE. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Images supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/29/vox-outdoor-galleria-mall_1787d10e00a_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[GO TO AN OUTDOOR CINEMA THIS WEEKEND: Outdoor theatres are an experience that allows movie lovers to watch their favourite films al fresco. Just before the weather heats up, now is the perfect time for guests to grab some warm popcorn and enjoy an open-air movie experience under a canopy of stars. One our favourite tried and tested spots is the OUTDOOR at Galleria Mall. Located on the rooftop of Galleria Mall, guests can choose from an oversized bean bag, single seats or upgrade to the VIP experience and stretch out on a cabana. OUTDOOR at Galleria Mall is also hosting kids’ screenings every weekend (Friday and Saturday at 6pm) so little film fans can enjoy the latest animation, action and adventure films. The experience is open till end of April to early May depending on the weather.  Standard Package for one priced at Dh137 (Sunday – Thursday)  and Dh157.50 (Friday & Saturday). The ticket includes one seat and F&B package with the choice of either nachos or a hot dog, salt or caramel popcorn, a soft drink, Evian water and a box of Monkey cookies. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/06/04/Ce-La-Vi-terrace_1727ec57f7e_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[TAKE ADVANTAGE OF DUBAI RESTAURANT WEEK DURING DFF: This year, not actually running just one week, but a whopping 17 days, Dubai Restaurant Week is a major player of DFF. Dubai Restaurant Week is a great opportunity for food fans to enjoy attractively-priced set meals at their favourite restaurants, or to take advantage of up to half price deals to experience somewhere new. Two-course lunches start at Dh95, while premium three-course dinner experiences start at Dh150.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Dry-Ager-guy_1788c2b439e_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[TRY THE DRY AGE BOUTIQUE TASTING EXPERIENCE: A novel concept and far cry from a typical butcher shop, visitors of the world’s only ‘dry aged meat boutique’ will be greeted by a record-breaking 8-metre-wide, triple glazed, Italian-crafted glass cold room where a premium selection of carefully sourced dry aged primal cuts are being displayed. Try something different this weekend and call the Dry Age Boutique for a tasting experience at the boutique itself or if you’d rather have a pairing with your meat, then you can experience the tasting at either Carters or Vintage grape bar. Contact the Dry Age Boutique directly for more information on the tasting experiences and how they can cater it to you. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/28/TEASER-FLOWER-1616929595227_17878839f5e_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[VISIT THE FLOWER FARM IN WADI ASIMAH:  The farm has around 30,000 stunningly gorgeous flowers. A sprawling flower farm which is hidden at Wadi Asimah, Fujairah is a must-visit place in UAE. The farm is open to the public from 6 am until 7 pm throughout the week, where approximately they receive 100-200 visitors in a day and about 400 visitors during the weekend. The owner Mohammed Al Mazroui has devoted more than seven years to keep his landscape blooming. ]]></media:title>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Public-Brunch-_1788bf24c4d_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[TRY THE NEW PUBLIC BRUNCH: The very popular Public restaurant in Dubai Mall has started serving brunch with plenty of delicious breakfast dishes on the menu. The Public Brunch was created in collaboration with the bakers of old Dubai to bring you an authentic experience to the heart of new Dubai. Their menu is offers dishes like the Buratta & Honey Bread, Zataar and Feta bread, Avocado and eggs on toast with basil sauce, Public truffle & egg puff and so much more. Plus they serve some of the best karak in town. Their bread is made by bakers in Satwa, who know the old Dubai and can recreate that authentic flavour. Stop by daily from 9am to 1pm.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/02/Dragon-Boat-Race_177f28b3dab_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[DUBAI DRAGON BOAT RACE: Taking place from April 2 to April 3, Dubai is playing host to the Dragon Boat Race, which sees hundreds of rowers competing against each other to win. The 200m races will take place on the water behind the Waterfront Market promenade throughout the two-day event. The teams will be divided into four race categories: Open, Mixed, Women & Corporate. For each race category teams will compete in heats, semi-finals and then the finals. The event will ensure COVID-19 safety measures are thoroughly implemented.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/ART-DUBAI-2-1617196995893_1788873d536_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[VISIT ART DUBAI:With a fresh programme and a new venue, Art Dubai is back with an in-person showcase. The first IRL art event on the global calendar, Art Dubai 2021 transcends the usual trappings of your typical art fair to symbolise something bigger. This year, mindful of the prevalent restrictions, Art Dubai moves to the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). Within its purpose-built venue set under the iconic Gate building, and with the Jumeirah Emirates Towers offering a befitting backdrop, the exhibition showcases 50 galleries from 31 countries, including ten of Dubai’s leading names, together with demonstrating the diversity that is informing the current contemporary design scene.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[AP]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/01/28/top-golf-dubai_17747d6d8c8_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[PLAY ANGRY BIRDS AT TOP GOLF: After a success in the USA, Topgolf is now also bringing its popular interactive Angry Birds Game to Dubai, meaning you can now play Angry Birds in real life from Topgolf Dubai’s tee-line. The Angry Birds game, which uses Topgolf's Toptracer ball-tracing technology, is family-friendly and for all ages and skill levels to enjoy. Guests will use Angry Birds characters as golf balls to smash down structures, defeat pigs, and earn as many points and stars as possible. Once you hit your golf ball, which will be the Angry Birds character Red or Bomb, they will take flight in hopes of causing mayhem. The player with the most points at the end of the game wins. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Shadow-Boxing_1788bfb5789_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[TRY SHADOWBOXING: Head to Rove La Mer Beach on Saturday, April 3, and join personal trainer Abdulla on the beach at 8.30am for a shadowboxing session. Shadowboxing is an exercise used in training for combat sports, especially, as its name implies, in boxing. It is used mainly to prepare the muscles for stronger physical activity. In shadowboxing, only one person is required to participate; the participant throws punches at no one in particular, in fun and exciting combinations. It’s a great full body workout, which helps to release energy and get you ready for anything that may come your way. ]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Souk-madinat-master-class_1788c0ad89d_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[LAST WEEKEND OF HOMEGROWN@SOUK FOOD FESTIVAL: Souk Madinat Jumeirah expands its schedule of ticketed F&B and kids’ masterclasses and gifts VeggiFoods goodness at popular venues during Souk Restaurant Week. This weekend there’s the Pasta making class for kids at Trattoria on Friday, April 2 at 12pm where Children will be able to make their own pasta, right from beating eggs, to kneading the dough and using tomato sauce from VeggiFoods produce, to rolling their pasta. Once cooked, youngsters can choose their favorite sauce before devouring their handmade creation. As for the adults, there’s a mixed beverage-making masterclass at Americano on Saturday, April 3 at 4pm: Guests can learn the art behind different blends through a mixed beverage masterclass at Americano, the trendy hangout spot.]]></media:title>
			<media:credit><![CDATA[Supplied]]></media:credit>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[India]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[India]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[d6356327-857f-41f5-bb96-2540b39f407c]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[India|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[india|world|asia|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[West Bengal elections 2021: Mamata-Suvendu face off in battleground Nandigram today]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[West Bengal elections 2021: Mamata-Suvendu face off in battleground Nandigram today]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Boots on the ground, ‘hawks’ in the sky as most talked-about seat in Bengal turns warzone]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/west-bengal-elections-2021-mamata-suvendu-face-off-in-battleground-nandigram-today-1.78249775</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Sanjib Kumar Das, Assistant Editor]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Mamata-Suvendu face off in Bengal’s Nandigram today]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Kolkata: It probably doesn’t get any bigger than this! Not in contemporary Bengal politics, that is. As the state enters the second phase of electioneering today, the most talked-about and high-stakes seat in this West Bengal assembly election goes to the polls, with Chief Minister and Trinamool Congress (TMC) supremo Mamata Banerjee locking horns with her bete noire Suvendu Adhikari, the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) candidate, in the Nandigram constituency in East Midnapore district. After today, there will still be six more phases left for these elections to conclude. Yet, no other seat, no other head-to-head will probably be talked about with the kind of interest and robust political point-counterpoint that this rural constituency in the hinterlands of Bengal has seen so far.</p>
<h3>The security challenge</h3>
<p>Twenty-two companies of paramilitary forces have been deployed in just this one constituency to ensure free and fair polls as the possibilities of violence are still high on the cards.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-210401-Nandigram33-1617264558611_1788c7ac215_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Voters stand in queue to cast their votes at a makeshift polling booth in Nandigram early on Thursday morning.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: AP</span></figcaption>
<p>Apart from the boots on the ground, there will be security personnel flying around on helicopters to keep a hawk-eye on polling booths deemed ‘sensitive’ by the Election Commission of India. This aerial security cover on election day is definitely a first for the state whose politics has left a trail of gore in election after election, particularly since 1972. In addition, Section 144 has been clamped on the entire constituency. In fact Nandigram is the only seat among the 30 that went to the polls today in the second phase to have Section 144 imposed on it and the entire area that falls under the Nandigram assembly segment has been sealed off since Tuesday night. Reports of attacks on BJP candidate Suvendu’s convoy have come in, while the body of a BJP worker was found hanging in Nandigram early on Thursday morning.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-210401-Nandigram-1617264552083_1788c7aa895_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Paramilitary personnel stand guard at a polling booth in Nandigram on Thursday.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: ANI</span></figcaption>
<h3>Nandigram’s tryst with destiny</h3>
<p>But beyond the violence, beyond the high-decibel campaigning, beyond all the debate and beyond the security scare, what probably sets Nandigram apart from the remaining 293 constituencies of the state is its political history since 2007, when 14 villagers were gunned down by the police as a massive crowd was protesting what they termed as “forceful” acquisition of agricultural land by the then Left Front government in the state led by the Communist Party of India (Marxist) for building a special economic zone for the purpose of industrialisation. Mamata, then the leader of the principal opposition party in the state, had utilised the land grab issue and the death of protesting peasants in Nandigram as the catapult to overthrow the CPI (M) from power, thereby terminating the longest running, democratically elected Communist government in the world. Mamata’s rise to power became synonymous with the Nandigram anti-land acquisition movement and it cemented the TMC leader’s image as a crusader for peasant rights and a champion of rural masses like no other political leader in Bengal had ever achieved.</p>
<h3>Why Mamata bit the bullet</h3>
<p>However, life seemed to have come a full circle for Mamata when she decided to move out of her pocket borough of Bhowanipore in South Kolkata and instead announce her intention to contest these elections from Nandigram.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-210401-Mamata552-1617264546569_1788c7a930d_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Mamata Banerjee, West Bengal Chief Minister and Trinamool Congress candidate from Nandigram, waves at her supporters during campaigning in Nandigram.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: ANI</span></figcaption>
<p>The irony is certainly not lost on the fact that the same Nandigram that had once paved the way for her rise as the state’s first female chief minister has today turned into a petri dish for a litmus test for not just her own popularity and her party’s fortunes in these polls, but may well decide the future course of her political career and that of her party’s as well. The same Nandigram that had once turned out to be her ace in breaching the CPI (M) citadel in Bengal has today made her bite the bullet and decide to contest these elections from there, knowing full well that she was hedging her bets like never before.</p>
<p>And it is little short of irony that in Nandigram, Mamata today is up against a candidate, who, until recently, was known to be one of her most trusted political aides. Suvendu, who was at one point of time Mamata’s “eyes and ears” in East Midnapore district in general and Nandigram in particular, is today a sworn enemy. And it is ironical indeed that the same Mamata who has always been taunting the BJP in Bengal as a force comprising “hired” mercenaries and a bunch of “outsiders”, is today herself being made to fend off the “outsider” barb from Suvendu and BJP in Nandigram.</p>
<h3>The minority vote</h3>
<p>For the record, Nandigram has roughly 262,000 voters. Of these, around 60,000 are Muslims. “This sizeable chunk of Muslim voters will definitely have a very crucial role to play in Nandigram. If a vast section of these Muslim voters once again size with TMC, then Suvendu’s defeat is certain. But the problem for the TMC is that first of all, there is a fair bit of resentment among a section of voters over the lack of fulfilment of electoral promises by the ruling party. There is a lot of disenchantment over the way relief measures were undertaken, or the lack of them, in the aftermath of the Amphan cyclone in Bengal last summer.</p>
<p>"Secondly, the presence of Meenakshi Mukherjee, the candidate for the Congress-Left combine in Nandigram may complicate the equation for TMC. With Abbas Siddiqui’s Indian Secular Front, a minority outfit, joining hands with the Congress-Left combine, the minority vote for TMC is no longer a ‘given’ — not in Nandigram, not anywhere else in the state,” Biswajit Bhattacharjee, a senior political analyst, told <em>Gulf News</em> from Nandigram late on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>“On the other hand, if the anti-establishment vote is split even marginally by the presence of a Congress-Left combine candidate in Nandigram, then it can create massive problems for Suvendu and BJP.</p><div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read more</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/opinion/op-eds/kerala-elections-2021-candidate-watch-thomas-issac-g-sudhakaran-and-v-muraleedharan---ministers-top-leaders-among-notable-omissions-1.1617196324189">Kerala Elections 2021 Candidate Watch: Thomas Issac, G Sudhakaran and V Muraleedharan - ministers, top leaders among notable omissions 
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/indian-border-state-manipur-withdraws-order-barring-shelter-for-those-fleeing-myanmar-1.1617108160443">Indian border state Manipur withdraws order barring shelter for those fleeing Myanmar
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/indias-daily-new-covid-19-infections-highest-in-more-than-five-months-1.78259413">India’s daily new COVID-19 infections highest in more than five months
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/india/maharashtra-karnataka-kerala-punjab-and-chhattisgarh-account-for-over-79-per-cent-of-active-covid-19-cases-in-india-1.78235642">Maharashtra, Karnataka, Kerala, Punjab and Chhattisgarh account for over 79 per cent of active COVID-19 cases in India
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<h3>Mamata, Suvendu on an even keel</h3>
<p>The other interesting factor in Nandigram this time around is the ‘silent’ voter who has so far not pledged his or her support publicly to any candidate. This silence is a bit unnerving for all major parties. But by and large, between Suvendu and Mamata, whoever manages to garner about 100,000 votes will definitely get that much closer to a win, though either way, the victory margin will be very thin,” Bhattacharjee added.</p><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-210401-Suvendu-1617264555122_1788c7ab474_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Union Home Minister and BJP leader Amit Shah during an election campaign rally in support of Suvendu Adhikari, the BJP candidate from Nandigram.
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: PTI</span></figcaption>
<p>For Mamata, it’s a prestige fight for sure. But more than that, it’s a fight that will probably serve as the bellwether for the rest of her career. For Suvendu, it’s a question of pulling out all the stops in his backyard. A win here and a majority for BJP in the state will raise his stature as a chief ministerial hopeful like never before.</p>
<p>So who’ll blink first? We’ll have to wait till May 2 for an answer to that. But for now, all eyes on Nandigram all through today for those tell-tale, very palpable signs that constitute polling-day chemistry at either end of the political spectrum. Keep watching.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.78249775</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.78249775]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 12:09:23+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 12:34:40+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-MAMATA-AND-SUVENDHU-1617264548862_1788c7a9bff_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/WIN-MAMATA-AND-SUVENDHU-1617264548862_1788c7a9bff_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Mamata Banerjee and Suvendu adhikari 

PHOTO PTI/ANI]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Op-Eds]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Op-Eds]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[415987d9-185d-4e9c-b629-64cc709800dd]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Op-Eds|India|Special-Reports|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|opinion|op-eds|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Kerala Elections 2021 Candidate Watch: Thomas Issac, G Sudhakaran and V Muraleedharan - ministers, top leaders among notable omissions ]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Kerala Elections 2021 Candidate Watch: Thomas Issac, G Sudhakaran and V Muraleedharan - ministers, top leaders among notable omissions ]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Some notable absentees in the Kerala elections this time and why they will be missed]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/opinion/op-eds/kerala-elections-2021-candidate-watch-thomas-issac-g-sudhakaran-and-v-muraleedharan---ministers-top-leaders-among-notable-omissions-1.1617196324189</link>
		<label><![CDATA[Comment]]></label>
		<author><![CDATA[Akhel Mathew, Special to Gulf News]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Kerala: Issac, Sudhakaran and other notable omissions]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<h2>T M Thomas Isaac: Standing out in a crowd of politicians</h2><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/Thomas-Issac_1788850f35d_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Thomas Issac
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Vijith Pulikkal/Gulf News</span></figcaption>
<p>For all the talk of Kerala’s high literacy, neither the state’s political parties nor its voters have shown any particular fancy for candidates with distinctly high academic qualifications. The bearded economist with a Marxian beard, T. M. Thomas Isaac has been an exception, winning from Mararikulam and Alappuzha constituencies multiple times. The two-time finance minister of Kerala with a PhD from the Centre for Development Studies in Kerala has often seemed an odd-ball in his party, the Communist Party of India Marxist, in which his colleagues are known for no-holds-barred aggression unlike Isaac who often draws parallels to his fiscal plans for the state with the writings of famous literary icons of the state.</p>
<p>This poll season is very different for Isaac, as it is for many CPM veterans because he isn’t contesting, in line with the party’s new-found policy to field new faces. So the man who talks of coir even if he is jolted from sleep, will braid new strategies for the party from the electoral ringside.</p>
<p>In recent times, he has been facing the heat over the Kerala Infrastructure Investment Fund, or KIIFB, for which he is being hauled over the coals for alleged failure in taking federal sanctions before raising masala bonds from abroad. In typical fashion, Isaac is using economic principles like a coir rope to strangulate his political opponents – saying that without KIIFB funds, the cash-strapped state’s development will come to a standstill, much like how the houseboats in his native Alappuzha district lie anchored in the COVID-19 impact.</p>
<h2>G Sudhakaran: An outspoken minister who gets things done</h2><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/03/31/G-Sudhakaran_17888521969_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Sudhakaran
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Vijith Pulikkal/Gulf News</span></figcaption>
<p>Kerala’s Communist Party of India Marxist is loaded with leaders who can be called stormy petrels, including P Jayarajan, E P Jayarajan and chief minister Pinarayi Vijayan himself. But even they fade away before G Sudhakaran, the veritable storm itself. Sudhakaran never minces words, and this time when he was denied a seat to contest, in line with the CPM policy to give emphasis to new faces, his supporters also did not mince words about what they thought about the decision.</p>
<p>“If G Sudhakaran is kept out, it will lead to losing the constituency. Does the party need continuity in rule? Is SDPI man Salam the replacement for G Sudhakaran? What assurance without G?” they demanded to know through posters that sprung in Alappuzha district.</p>
<p>Sudhakaran is bluntly outspoken, and most of his fulminations have been on the subject of roads and bridges, given his portfolio of public works in the outgoing Pinarayi Vijayan ministry. For all his rants, public works in Kerala are of questionable quality, and long delayed. In his own native Alappuzha district a flyover that was in the making for 45 years got completed only this year.</p>
<p>When he is not delivering a scathing sermon to someone, Sudhakaran sometimes takes time off to pen some lines, apparently wanting to prove how he can construct lyrical lines just as he can oversee road and bridge projects. But the part-time poet met his match recently when he took on Twenty20 founder-leader Sabu M Jacob, alleging that Jacob was constructing “my roads” without permission. To that, Jacob retorted, “I can give back those roads, but please give me some time – to hand it over in the manner they were, complete with potholes”. Sometimes, part-time poets do get poetic justice.</p>
<h2>Mullappally Ramachandran: Walking a tightrope</h2><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Mullappally-Ramachandran_1788b95ec6a_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">Mullappally Ramachandran
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Vijith Pulikkal/Gulf News</span></figcaption>
<p>In the political merry-go-round that has been a norm in Kerala for over four decades, the Left Democratic Front and the United Democratic Front come to power alternately, assuring each front of power every five years.</p>
<p>What is feared by the UDF is that the merry-go-round may not play out that way this time as different surveys point to a repeat of the LDF government. That should give the shivers to Mullappally Ramachandran, the bespectacled, moustachioed president of the Kerala Pradesh Congress Committee.</p>
<p>He himself has opted out of the poll fray, but that only adds to the expectations of him leading the Congress to victory. In 2016, the Congress-led UDF could only muster 47 seats to LDF’s 91 and this time internal bickering, heartburns over candidate selection and the diminishing clout of Congress on a national scale are all adding to the enormity of Ramachandran’s task.</p>
<p>The exit of a senior leader like P C Chacko from the party to join the Nationalist Congress Party is the latest proof of the mood in the Congress ranks in Kerala. And Ramachandran also has to walk a tight rope in dealing with the chief ministerial ambitions of Ramesh Chennithala and Oommen Chandy, even though it will be an issue only if the UDF wins.</p>
<p>Former Congress president Rahul Gandhi has already spent many days in Kerala, swimming in the sea with fishermen, chatting up crowds thronging his campaign vehicle and addressing campaign meetings. But Ramachandran may still be left with an eerie feeling that this time Keralites may just decide to change their five-year itch for change.</p>
<h2>V Muraleedharan: The minister who won't be running this time</h2><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/V-Muraleedharan_1788b96d4e3_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">V Muraleedharan
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Vijith Pulikkal/Gulf News</span></figcaption>
<p>Despite the Bharatiya Janata Party’s bull run across India, particularly since 2014, there has been one fortress that has remained near-impregnable to the party, namely Kerala. To break that frustrating political standing of the party in Kerala is the brief of 63-year-old V Muraleedharan, a Rajya Sabha MP and the federal minister of state for external affairs.</p>
<p>The BJP presently has one seat in Kerala’s 140-strong assembly, namely the Nemom constituency. The party’s candidate at Nemom this time, Kummanam Rajasekharan likes to call it ‘Kerala’s Gujarat’, but the fact is that it is not an easy task for the BJP to retain even that one seat.</p>
<p>However, as Muraleedharan emerges a key campaigner for the BJP in Kerala, there are several positives for him to bank on, like technocrat E Sreedharan’s decision to join the party and contest from Palakkad, and the possibility of winning a few constituencies where the BJP had put up impressive shows in 2016 but had not won.</p>
<p>The BJP in Kerala has long been a house divided, known for internal bickering, which means extra effort for campaigners like Muraleedharan to lift the party’s fortunes from the present status as a single-seat outfit.</p>
<p>One would expect Muraleedharan to be careful with words, given his portfolio of external affairs, but his gaffes have been the delight of social media trollers. His defence of the federal government’s frequent raising of fuel prices by arguing that “the rise in domestic fuel price has not been as much as the fall in international crude price” has been among the most widely circulated trolls among Keralites.</p>
<p>But even then, Muraleedharan and the BJP are hoping to have more seats in Kerala, where the BJP has bloomed in just one seat. One more seat would be a 100 per cent growth for the party.</p>
<h2>P Jayarajan: An&nbsp;omission loaded with meanings</h2><img src="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/P-Jayarajan_1788b97dde8_original-ratio.jpg" />

 <figcaption class="image-caption">P Jayarajan
 <span class="image-credit">Image Credit: Vijith Pulikkal/Gulf News</span></figcaption>
<p>If horses are for courses, few fit the bill for the political rough-and-tumble in Kerala’s Malabar region better than Communist Party of India Marxist leader P Jayarajan. The former MLA and former district president of the Students’ Federation of India was attacked by alleged RSS activists in August 1999 at his house at Kathiroor that left him with crippling injuries. And then he himself was named one of the accused in the conspiracy to murder RSS leader Kathiroor Manoj in 2014.</p>
<p>Since then, the aggressive CPM leader’s image has taken a dent and it didn’t help when a division bench of the Kerala High Court refused to stay a single bench’s order to invoke the provisions of the Unlawful Activities (Prevention) Act (UAPA) against Jayarajan and the other accused.</p>
<p>Most senior CPM leaders in Kerala have staunch fan followings in their respective regions, but P Jayarajan stands out distinctly even among them. He has a ‘PJ Army’ page on Facebook, run by his fans who are his staunch supporters. So when he was denied a seat, the PJ Army criticised the move in public domain, a practice that the CPM does not brook.</p>
<p>Jayarajan’s supporters suspect that chief minister Pinarayi Vijayan himself is behind the strings being pulled to side-line one of Malabar’s most powerful leaders in the party. But given Pinarayi’s political ascendancy, the PJ Army may be left to fight twin battles – a political one against Pinarayi Vijayan and a legal one to extricate their dear leader from the Kathiroor Manoj murder case.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617196324189</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617196324189]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 07:47:10+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 08:05:52+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kerala-elections-2021_1788b944f7e_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Kerala-elections-2021_1788b944f7e_original-ratio.jpg">
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Pakistan]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Pakistan]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[60d9354f-ecd0-4701-bd23-6fc2cd57f6dd]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Pakistan|World|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[pakistan|world|asia|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[Watch: Young boy from Pakistan's Sikh community performs traditional Pashtun dance, video goes viral]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[Watch: Young boy from Pakistan's Sikh community performs traditional Pashtun dance, video goes viral]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[The viral video shows his dance skills as the audience cheers on him]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/pakistan/watch-young-boy-from-pakistans-sikh-community-performs-traditional-pashtun-dance-video-goes-viral-1.1617264625538</link>
		<author><![CDATA[ANI]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Pakistan's Sikh boy dance video goes viral]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Islamabad:&nbsp;&nbsp;A young boy Sikh boy in Pakistan took the internet by storm with his performance of 'Attan', a traditional Pashtun  dance, during a wedding in Pakistan.</p>
<p>Identified as Jagraj Singh by The Express Tribune, the boy from Pakistan's Sikh community in Peshawar is seen in a video dancing to the beats of the rubab played by local musician Gurmeet Singh</p>
<p>In the video that has gone viral, the boy is seen wearing a blue kurta, white pant and a black patka while he jives to the folk dance as the audience cheers him on.</p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CNFRRyUqHeI/" data-show-caption="true" data-embed class="social-embed"></a>

<p>On Instagram, the boy's video gained over 18,329 views and the comments section filled up with praise for the little dancer. "Normalise dancing not just boys but everyone," wrote one user on the picture-sharing app.</p>
<p>"Love his moves," wrote another user.</p>
<p>Whereas on Twitter, the video gained over 158 likes and has been retweeted 39 times."This moment is very memorable and pleasant for family #SikhCommunity in Pakistan," a user wrote on Twitter.</p>
<p>Attan originated in the Pashtun areas of Afghanistan and Pakistan and typically the dance is done in a circle with dancers spininning and often swirling scarves in the air. Attan songs are long and sometimes dancing continue hours and hours in the night.</p>]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617264625538</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617264625538]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 12:08:24+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 12:38:17+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Boy-from-Pakistan-s-Sikh-community-performs-traditional-dance--video-goes-viral-._1788c797b6d_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2021/04/01/Boy-from-Pakistan-s-Sikh-community-performs-traditional-dance--video-goes-viral-._1788c797b6d_original-ratio.jpg">
		</media:content>

	</item>
	<item>
		<primarycategory><![CDATA[Retail]]></primarycategory>
		<mainsectioncssclass><![CDATA[Retail]]></mainsectioncssclass>
		<categoryid><![CDATA[e02bc36b-b9f0-47c5-9e23-1ac27df7171e]]></categoryid>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail|]]></category>
		<adtags><![CDATA[]]></adtags>
		<articleType><![CDATA[standardArticle]]></articleType>
		<visualType>image</visualType>
	<department><![CDATA[blank|business|retail|]]></department>
		<title><![CDATA[UAE gold shoppers in no rush to buy again, wait for prices to go below Dh190/gm]]></title>
		<linkcopy><![CDATA[UAE gold shoppers in no rush to buy again, wait for prices to go below Dh190/gm]]></linkcopy>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[For now, they are better off waiting for gold prices to settle down]]></shortdescription>
		<link>https://gulfnews.com/business/retail/uae-gold-shoppers-in-no-rush-to-buy-again-wait-for-prices-to-go-below-dh190gm-1.1617246903603</link>
		<author><![CDATA[Manoj Nair]]></author>
		<linktext><![CDATA[Why rush? UAE gold shoppers wait for -Dh190/gm level ]]></linktext>
		<highlightsTitle><![CDATA[Highlights]]></highlightsTitle>
		<highlights><![CDATA[]]></highlights>
		<description><![CDATA[
<p>Dubai: Local gold prices will need to drop to Dh185 a gram or below for UAE shoppers to rush back to buying their favourite metal.</p>
<p>“Shoppers need to see a drop to a new level to be convinced there’s value in buying at that price,” said a jewellery retailer in Dubai. “Any price drop to under Dh190 could convince them – but the best outcome would be if and when gold drops to under Dh185.”</p>
<p>For the record, Dubai rates for 22K were at or around the Dh170 a gram mark in March last year, which was the lowest point in these 12 months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Gold’s been under some pressure in recent days in the international metals market, but on Thursday morning has shot up by nearly $30 to head back to $1,709 an ounce levels. In Dubai, the overnight price for 22K is Dh193.25 a gram, and that could see an increase by Dh1 or so when the new rate for this morning is set at 9am.</p>
<p>Even with the recent price drop, there was no rush to the shops, according to gold industry sources in Dubai. “The store traffic in these days was just about steady, there was some pick up during the ‘Holi’ day – but on the whole shoppers have gotten used to gold rates of Dh194-Dh196 a gram.</p>
<p>“The impression is that gold prices could come down and test minus Dh190 levels – UAE shoppers are waiting for that to happen.” (The Indian festival of Holi was marked on March 28.)</p><div class="more-similar-article">
<h3 class="text-uppercase similar-title">Read More</h3>
    <ul>
<li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/photos/business/look-uae-shoppers-learn-to-wait-for-gold-price-dip-1.1615445054732">Look: UAE shoppers learn to wait for gold price dip
</a></li><li> <a href="https://gulfnews.com/business/company-releases/malabar-gold-commits-200m-on-new-store-additions-this-year-1.1617012798489">Malabar Gold commits $200m on new store additions this year
</a></li></ul>
</div>
<h3>Will prices drop?</h3>
<p>Despite Thursday’s spike, gold industry watchers reckon that international prices could fall to around $1,660-$1,680 an ounce levels. If that happens, Dubai gold rates could range in the Dh185-Dh188 a gram. And that would be the decisive point for shoppers and jewellery retailers alike.</p>
<p>Through the last six months, gold buyers have retuned only for special buying occasions such as the ‘Diwali’ and ‘Dhanteras’ festivals or for the end-of-year gifting occasions. Through most of this period, gold was in the Dh200-Dh208 a gram range.</p>
<p>The upcoming World Gold Council first quarter 2021 numbers will provide an accurate indication of demand patterns for retail level gold and jewellery buying.</p><div class="fact-box">
    <div class="fact-box-title">The next big buy date</div>
    <div class="fact-box-content">UAE shoppers will be hoping that gold prices would drop to slightly more accessible levels by May... and especially by May 14. 

That's when the Indian festival of 'Akshaya Tritiya' - the Indian festival rated as most auspicious to buy gold or other assets - falls this year. "It's the one major occasion customers as all as retailers look forward too," said Cyriac Varghese, General Manager of Sky Jewellery. 

"Buying is assured during those days - but any additional drop in prices will mark a sizable improvement in volumes."</div>
    </div>
]]></description>
		<guid>1.1617246903603</guid>
		<rsslink><![CDATA[https://gulfnews.com/rss/?generatorName=mrss&articleId=1.1617246903603]]></rsslink>
		<pubDate>2021-04-01 07:03:47+0400</pubDate>
		<modifieddate>2021-04-01 07:38:40+0400</modifieddate>
		<enclosure url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/10/15/STOCK-Dubai-gold-shopping_1752c3865da_medium.jpg" length="2000" type="image/jpeg"/> 
		<media:content medium="image" type="image/jpg" url="https://imagevars.gulfnews.com/2020/10/15/STOCK-Dubai-gold-shopping_1752c3865da_original-ratio.jpg">
			<media:title><![CDATA[Dubai gold shopping at Gold souq]]></media:title>
		</media:content>

	</item>
</channel>
</rss>